cookitsimply.com 2009-04-13

# COOKITSIMPLY.COM: Privacy policy

## information

COOKITSIMPLY.COM is continuously committed to protecting the privacy of it's visitors. We do not sell, distribute or give out any of our visitors information. The following discloses how information is collected and used on and throughout our web site. Aside from the case where you explicitly give permission to provide your contact information to a third party, any personal information you provide on this site will be only be known to yourself and COOKITSIMPLY.COM. 

## personal information and demographics

COOKITSIMPLY.COM does not collect any personally identifiable information about you such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address, unless you actively provide this by filling out registration forms. 

However, COOKITSIMPLY.COM does obtain some types of non-personally identifiable information such as your IP address, your browser type and operating system, and the address of the web site that referred you to COOKITSIMPLY.COM. This information is collected as a whole for a broad range of _general_ statistical uses; for providing potential advertisers with audience statistics, for administrating the web site, providing more-focused in-demand content, and to track abusive users. 

## registration/contributions

A user or visitor that submits content to COOKITSIMPLY.COM must first be a registered member and hence provide their name and a working e-mail address, along with account information and _optional_ personal details. All information provided, except passwords, may be listed on the web site and should be considered public. 

## polls and voting

None of these features require you to provide any personal information, however COOKITSIMPLY.COM stores your IP address along with your answer or vote. This is solely to avoid multiple votes from the same person, and COOKITSIMPLY.COM will never disclose your IP address to anybody else. 

## disclaimer

This site contains links to other sites and COOKITSIMPLY.COM can not be held responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites. 

## further information

If you have additional questions regarding your privacy on Cookitsimply.com, feel free to contact us using the menu.
